seic.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy | SEI

_Effective as of December, 2017_

SEI (“us”, “our” or “we”) appreciates that you have provided us with your personal information and protecting that information is an important part of how we conduct our business. We believe it is important for you to know how we treat information about you that we may receive from this site (“Site” or “online services”). Our online services are not directed to or intended for individuals under 18 years of age. By visiting this Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## Information collected

The types of personal information that may be collected at our Site include: name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. We will not sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information to others in contravention of this Privacy Policy. Please contact us to update your account information whenever such information ceases to be complete or accurate.

We collect information about how you use our website. This information includes collecting your IP address and any other information sent by your browser. This site uses cookies (files sent by us to your computer) and may store information about you, which we can access when you visit our site. We do this in order to assist in pre-filling forms (so you don’t have to enter the same information twice), as well as direct to you to the last SEI regional site you visited. You can accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser settings. To do so, refer to the instructions for your file management software. Our cookies will include the file name “@www.seic.com”. By deleting or declining cookies, you may not be able to use some interactive features or access certain areas of the site that depend on cookies.

## Do not track policy

We do not engage in the collection of personal information about your online activities over time and across third-party Web sites or online services and do not allow third parties to collect personal information about your online activities over time and across third-party Web sites when you use our online services. We do not respond to Web browser “do not track signals”.

## Use of collected information

We may use information you provide us through our online services to:

  * Respond to your questions and requests
  * Provide specified services to you
  * Send you marketing or educational communications that we believe may be of interest to you
  * Comply with laws, regulations, legal processes and law enforcement requirements
  * For any other purpose outlined in this Privacy Policy and/or the Terms of Use, and as permitted by law

You can stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from SEI by following the specific instructions set forth in any promotional e-mail you receive from us. You may also have the option of proactively making choices about the communications you receive from particular SEI Web Properties or services.

We welcome online feedback and provide forums for feedback, such as but not limited to article ratings and comments. Any communication transmitted to SEI or otherwise provided to us via the Site ("Submission") is understood by both parties to be non-confidential and non-proprietary. We have no obligation with respect to any Submission and may freely copy, reproduce, incorporate, distribute, or use such Submission as it wishes. Submissions that are violent, obscene, threatening, defamatory, libelous, or violate the law in any way, are prohibited.

## Our security procedures

Our goal is to protect your personal information submitted to us through our online services. We maintain reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable law to guard nonpublic personal information you have provided to us through our online services. We have internal policies governing the proper handling of consumer information by personnel and requiring third parties that provide support services on our behalf to adhere to appropriate security standards with respect to such information.

## Links to other sites

We may establish links between this Site and websites operated by third parties. Your access to and use of such linked websites is governed by the terms of use and privacy policies of those sites. SEI disclaims responsibility for the privacy policies and customer information practices of third-party internet websites hyperlinked from our Website.

## International users

This Privacy Policy is provided in accordance with and subject to applicable U.S. law. If you decide to continue to access our online services from your location outside the United States, you hereby agree that your use of those services is subject to this Online Privacy Policy and your personal information may be transferred or processed in the United States.

## Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to modify or supplement this Online Privacy Policy at any time. Therefore, we recommend that you review this Online Privacy Policy, updated and posted on this Site, regularly for changes. The Effective Date of this Online Privacy Policy, as stated above, indicates the last time this Online Privacy Policy was revised or materially changed.

**See also:  ** **Terms of Use**
